A Guide to the Near East Foundation records, Fred and Carrie Midgley papers, Accession 2012:071, RG 6 FA1309
Rockefeller Archive Center
Near East Foundation records, Fred and Carrie Midgley papers, Accession 2012:071, RG 6
1926-1928
Rockefeller Archive Center
Near East Foundation
Near East Relief (Organization)
FA1309
0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged item may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
Separated Materials
Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Scope and Contents
The Midgley papers focus on efforts in Greece and Syria.
- Near East Foundation records, Fred and Carrie Midgley papers, Accession 2012:071, 1926-1928; 6; 0.76 Cubic Feet
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volume I Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volume II Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Volume II Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Volume II Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Volume II Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Volume II Midgley Near East Relief Syra, Greece, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 5)